ALFONZO TAMAÑO

VIDEO EDITOR/DEVELOPER



- +63 950 835 8986
- ✓ akilabiel3@gmail.com
- Philippines
 - alfonzo-video-portfolio.netlify.app

PROFILE

Experienced photo/video editor with close to three years of dedicated expertise, utilizing a range of industry-standard software such as Adobe Animate, Premiere Pro, After Effects, and CapCut. Demonstrated versatility by producing high-quality content across various video genres, including films, 2D animations, commercials, documentaries, and vlogs. Eager to expand horizons and apply expertise to create engaging content in new genres.

SKILLS

- Web Development
- · Photo and Video Editing
- Programming
- UI/UX Design
- Troubleshooting
- Problem Solving
- Collaboration
- Communication

EXPERIENCE

VIDEO EDITING

Freelance

2020 - Present

- · Improves color grading
- · Added motion tracking
- Gets to animation
- Having a transition

WEB DEVELOPMENT/PROGRAMMING

Freelance

2021 - Present

- A website with API integration
- · Created own portfolio
- Can use various frameworks
- Lot of programming languages

CUSTOMER SUPPORT

Microsoft via Directly

October 2022 - September 2023

- Handled different types of customers
- Managing two to three tickets at the same time
- 6-8 hours of working (free time)

EDUCATION

SOPHOMORE

2022-PRESENT

Dizon High Memorial National High School

2020-22

JUNIOR AND SENIOR YEAR

Mapua Malayan Colleges Laguna